Ah, that's cute.
あ、可愛いですね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I'm excited.
ドキドキしてます
Are you excited?
ドキドキしてる?
Why are you excited?
なんでドキドキしてる?
My mind goes blank.
頭真っ白になっちゃうよ
Will it turn white?
真っ白になっちゃう?
That's right.
そうだよね
All of a sudden, I get nervous when the camera is being used like this.
急にね、こんなカメラ回されて緊張しちゃうよね
I'll take a moment to think about what I'm going to do next.
ちょっと、これから何するか想像つけます
It's cute.
可愛いね
How old are you now?
今何歳?
I'm 19 years old.
19歳です
What do you usually do?
普段は何してる?
I'm an idol.
アイドルやってます
How long have you been doing what?
どのくらい何やってる?
It's really fun.
めっちゃ楽しいです
Do you want to perform live?
ライブしたりとか?
How much?
どのくらい?
Do you do it every week?
毎週やる?
Every week.
毎週
What is that?
それは何かあれ?
Local?
地方の?
Where are you doing it?
ど こでやってるの?
I usually do it in Fukuoka and then in Tokyo.
いつもは福岡でやって、東京で
A handshake press conference?
握手会見とか?
An instax press conference?
チェキ会見とか?
Check press conferences, etc.
チ ェキ会見とか
May I?
いいですか?
picture?
え?
What should I do?
どうしようかな?
Awkward?
気まずい?
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
happy?
嬉しい?
What about your boyfriend?
彼氏は?
I'm not there.
いないです
Are you being told that you're not there?
いないって言わされてる?
Isn't that just what the agency told you to do?
事務所から言わされてるだけじゃない?
Really.
本当に
Have you ever done anything naughty?
エッチなことしたことある?
having done something naughty
エッチなことをしたこと
be.
ある
Fukuoka?
福 岡?
What if it's the last thing?
最後にしたら?
It's a little scary to count.
ちょっとカウントするの怖いぐらい
What is the average number of people?
平均人数は?
Only that person.
その人だけ
Alone?
一人?
That's what I've been told too.
それも言わされてるんだよね
No.
違います
Ubu, see you then.
ウーブだね、じゃあね
Wow, I just heard that it's naughty.
すごいさっき聞いたらエッチなの
A little naughty.
ちょっとエッチ
You're so horny inside your head.
頭の中がエッチだよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I did it.
やっちゃった
You're going to have sex alone, right?
一人エッチするんでしょ
When do you do it?
どういう時にするの?
Suddenly, I suddenly felt a little horny.
ふとした時に、急にちょっとムラムラしちゃって、
I ran into the restroom of a commercial facility and
商 業施設のトイレに駆け込んで、
Alone.
一人で
For toilets in commercial facilities.
商業施設のトイレに
When I went to a barre show, when I was shopping.
バレコとか行った時、 買い物してる時
It seems like timing.
タイミングみたい
There might not be one person right now.
今、一人ないかも
Are you going to the toilet?
トイレ行くの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Alone.
一人で
What should I do?
どうしよう
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Is it okay?
いいの?
Well then, just a little.
じゃあちょっと
I'm so horny.
ム ラムラって
On the contrary, it makes me nervous.
逆に緊張するんだけどな
神聖水田
It's so cute.
すげえ可愛いね
It's Beidel after all.
やっぱバイデルだね
Is there something?
何かあるの?
I guess you could call it a decisive line.
決め台詞っていうか
Decisive line?
決め台詞?
Introducing myself.
自分紹介
I want you to think about the decisive line together.
決め台詞、一緒に考えてほしい
What color is it?
何色なの?
There are colors, right?
色はあるでしょ?
There are colors.
色はある
white?
白?
Together.
合わせて
That's right.
そうなんだ
So it's white.
それで白だね
This is dangerous.
やばいじゃん、これ
I'm glad I'm not a fan.
俺がファンじゃなくてよかったのよ
good.
よかった
Physically.
物理的に
Physically?
物 理的に?
no matter how?
どんなに?
What is that?
ど んなことか
It's like a hedge image.
ヘッジな映像みたいな
Like AMA.
AMAみたいな
Squirting or something.
潮吹きとか
Do you get excited when you see squirting?
潮吹き見ると興奮するの?
Excited.
興奮する
Have you ever squirted?
潮吹いたことある?
Is there one?
あるの?
Sometimes I get touched too much.
たまに触られすぎる
It makes me feel good.
気持ちよくなっちゃう
fun?
楽しい?
I want to discover it.
発見したいわ
It's really scary though.
めっちゃ怖いんだけど
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'm scared.
怖くしてる
Are you scared?
怖くしてる?
I'm touching nature
自然に触っちゃってる
Yo.
よ
Those are heavy clothes.
重 い服だね
favorite.
お気に入り
I have a lot of favorites.
お気に入り広いな
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
Smooth.
すべすべ
I'm nervous and my legs are shaking.
緊張して足がぐるぐるしてる
I can see it.
見えちゃう
I just realized it.
今気がついた
Are you being filmed?
撮られてる?
Maybe.
もしかして
Being photographed.
撮られてる
I've been taking pictures all the time.
ずっと撮ってるよ
It's pure white.
真っ白だね
nervous
緊張して
Ru.
る
scared.
怖 い
What should I do?
どうしよう
amazing.
すごい
It's really growing.
めっちゃ伸びてる
What should I do?
どうしよう
This is terrible.
やばいです
What should I do?
どうしよう
As a foot.
足として
Is this okay?
これでいいんですか?
The soles of my feet are dirty now.
私は今足の裏が汚いから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You'll do it, idol.
やるでしょ、アイドル
I won't do it.
やらないよ
やらない
It feels real.
リアルに感じてる
In real life?
リ アルに?
yes.
そう
A little amazing.
ちょっとすごい
This Shincho is too cute.
このシンチョは 可愛すぎるね
Oh no.
やば
amazing.
すごい
forever?
ずっと?
I'll take it off.
脱いちゃう
picture?
え?
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃう?
now?
今?
Here?
ここで?
Don't look at Jurjuru.
ジュルジュル見ないで
You can go from below.
下からいけるから
There's still the most.
まだ一番あるね
What should I do?
どうしよう
It's folded neatly.
綺麗に畳んでる
terrible.
やばい
Just like that.
あんまに
Don't look at Jurjuru.
ジュルジュル見ないで
It's really growing.
めっちゃ伸びてる
Like a tea bag.
ティーバッグみたいな
It's true.
本当だ
I completely forgot.
すっかり忘れてた
I don't know why.
どうしてんのかわからない
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だ
Will it be a swimsuit?
水着になったりする?
I go to the bathroom with my friends.
友達とトイレ行ったりするんだけどね
Look.
見てよ
I'll do it just in case.
一応するから
It's up.
アップだ
アップだよ
I'm going to be photographed.
撮られちゃいす
I can't take pictures.
撮れない
It's beautiful, after all.
綺麗だな、やっぱり
Guard.
ガードして
What should I do?
どうしたらいい?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だよ
I don't understand at all.
全然わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
What is that?
なにそれ?
Are you seriously drawing?
マジ描いてる?
A little bit here too...
ここもちょっと...
It's a bit warm though.
薄気あったかいんだけど
Very
めっちゃ
Because I'm sleeping.
寝 てるから
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
What a pose.
なんてポーズだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Should I take care of it?
お手入れしてきたほうがいいですか?
Don't take care of it.
お手入れしないで
Don't take care of it?
お手入れしないで?
It's okay, you're doing it.
よくだわ、してるでしょ
I came in the morning.
朝やってきたけど
It's hell.
地獄だ
地獄?
It's a pose from hell.
地獄のポーズだ
It's kind of small.
なんかちっちゃいね
Oh no, that's my signature.
やばい、その自分のサインは
I don't know.
わかんないよね
My body is stiff!
体硬っ!
Like this?
こうやって?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Feels good, feels good.
いい感じ、いい感じ
a little bit.
ちょっと
Nice, this embarrassing feeling.
いいね、この恥ずかしい感じがね
That's pretty serious, that reaction now.
結構ガチです、今その反応
It's really nice.
めっちゃいいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
No.
ダメ
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
You're too sensitive.
敏感すぎるね
I really wanted to include it.
本気で入れて欲しくなっちゃった
I've heard that you might break your finger.
指折れそうなの聞いてるけど
river
か わ
good.
いい
It's so cute.
め っちゃかわいい
To my surprise, it felt really good.
びっくりしたらめっちゃ気持ちよくて
What should I do?
どうしよう
Is that so?
そうなの?
You can take a picture somewhere.
どっかで撮ってもいいね
What should I do?
どうしよう
I'll do it just in case.
一応しちゃう
what?
何?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm curious.
気になってしまう
Very serious.
すっごいまじまじと
As an impression.
感想として
Feels good.
気 持 ちいい
You're good at it.
上手だね
good?
上手?
everytime?
いつも?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
It's going to be delicious.
美味しくなっちゃう
What should I do?
どうしよう
That's amazing.
すっごいね
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
Over here.
こっちで
terrible.
やばい
That's terrible.
やばいね
That's amazing.
すごいね
That's terrible.
やばいね
What is dangerous?
やばいって何?
amazing.
すごい
It's dangerous though.
危ないんだけど
dangerous?
危ない?
big.
大きい
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
I'm almost alive.
生きそうになっちゃってる
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
I'll call you many times.
何回も呼ぶよ
It's really difficult for me to take pictures.
自分が撮ってるのがめっちゃ難しい
Awesome.
す っごい
Say it again.
もう一回言って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Where's your dick?
ちんちんどこ?
I want you to put your dick in here too.
ちんちんもここに入れてほしい
It's not in yet.
まだ入ってないよ
amazing.
すごい
Trying to bring it in.
入れてこようとして
tight.
きつい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's really tough though.
めちゃくちゃきついんだけど
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It's super tight though.
超きついんだけど
I don't know.
分かんない
I don't know if I'm too harsh.
自 分がきついか分かんないけど
tight.
きつい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
It's so hot
い っちゃ
cormorant?
う?
Shall we go?
い っちゃう?
tight
き つ
stomach.
い
What should I do?
どう しよう
Shall we go right away?
すぐいっちゃう?
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Isn't it early?
早くない?
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
amazing.
すごい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
I'm going.
いっちゃう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
once again.
もう一度
eye
め
It's so cute.
っちゃ かわいい
terrible.
やばい
It feels super good.
超気持ちいい
What should I do?
どうしよう
It's moving a lot.
めっちゃ動いてる
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
I'm going.
行っちゃう
go.
行 く
terrible.
やばい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
difficult.
難しい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Wave your hand behind your back.
後ろに手を振って
Spread your legs.
足を広げて
Like this.
こうやって
Move it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れして
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That again.
またそれ
go.
行く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
What should I do?
どうしよう
It's beautiful.
きれいだね
I can see it.
見えるね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
once again.
もう一度
difficult.
難しい
Shoulder peter.
肩ペター
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
The air is hot.
空気が熱い
Feels good.
気持ちいい
go.
行く
I'm going.
行っちゃう
go.
行く
But I can't.
できないんだけど
What should I do?
どう しよう
どうしていい?
Just like that.
そのまま
I can't.
できないよ
I want to go.
行きたいんだけど
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Can I take it out?
出していいの?
I keep going.
行きまくりだ
Going
行き
It's a makuri.
ま くりだ
I keep going.
行きまくりだ